<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Argument About History</title>
    <link href="/2024/01/24/Argument%20About%20History/"/>
    <url>/2024/01/24/Argument%20About%20History/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://pics3.baidu.com/feed/500fd9f9d72a6059a329be523c3a789c033bba56.jpeg?token=73550d4d35d422b59f0ff81d126e5aa1" alt="History"><br>Some people think it is important for all children to learn history in school. Others believe that<br>other subjects are more relevant to children’s lives today. But in my opinion, making history a “mandatory” subject is very important.</p><p>Supporters of teaching history to all children assert that it offers valuable insights into the development of societies, cultures, and civilizations. Knowledge of historical events allows individuals to comprehend the roots of current issues and developments, fostering critical thinking skills and a sense of identity. Additionally, history connects individuals to their heritage, instilling national pride.</p><p>Opponents argue that in today’s fast-paced world, certain subjects like Chinese, Mathematics, English and Science are more directly applicable to children’s lives. They emphasize practical skills that can be immediately applied in real-life situations.</p><p>In my opinion, a balanced approach is crucial. While acknowledging the importance of practical subjects, history provides a crucial understanding of our roots and helps develop critical thinking skills. A well-rounded education system should integrate various disciplines, allowing students to appreciate the significance of historical knowledge alongside acquiring skills pertinent to the present and future.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>English-composition</category>
      
      <category>Argument</category>
      
      <category>History</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>History</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>A popular Chinese traditional food——Zongzi</title>
    <link href="/2024/01/14/A%20popular%20Chinese%20traditional%20food%E2%80%94%E2%80%94Zongzi/"/>
    <url>/2024/01/14/A%20popular%20Chinese%20traditional%20food%E2%80%94%E2%80%94Zongzi/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="https://img0.baidu.com/it/u=734678289,3305521186&fm=253&fmt=auto&app=138&f=JPEG?w=500&h=375" alt="粽子"><br>In our country, we have a lot of delicious traditional dishes. One of them is known as “zongzi”. We all like eating it very much.<br>First of all, let’s talk about how the zongzi is made. To make it, we need to prepare some reed leaves, glutinous rice, and other fillings. First, the glutinous rice should be soaked one night in advance before we wrap the zongzi. After the soaked glutinous rice is dried, we need to add an appropriate amount of red beans to the glutinous rice, stir it evenly, and then add some soy sauce, oyster sauce, and stir it evenly again. In this way, the zongzi will be more fragrant. Then, we should put the reed leaves into boiling water and boil them for about two minutes in order to make the leaves become soft and wrap the zongzi more easily. After all of that, you can start wrapping the zongzi. First, fold the reed leaves into a funnel shape. Then, add some fillings to the “funnel” and press it down tightly. At last, close the leaves and tie it up with beautiful threads. You can put it into the cold water and boil it. After all of that, you can only wait for a long time. I believe it will be delicious.<br>Some people might ask that when we eat it. We eat it for a poet named Qu Yuan. The poet Qu Yuan had an immense love to his country. As the reason, he helped the king of Chu administer the country so that the country would be more strong. But after a few years, another country named Qin attacked his country and occupied his country. Qu Yuan was very sorrowful. So, on the fifth day of the fifth lunar month, Qu Yuan threw himself into the Miluo River, and died for his country. The people didn’t want the fish eat Qu Yuan. They threw the bamboo tube with rice into the river. After a long time, we always eat the zongzi on the fifth day of the fifth lunar month.<br>The zongzi is very important in my home country. We eat it for commemorating Qu Yuan. We will never forget him. The food is not only delicious but also memorable. We like it very much forever.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>English-composition</category>
      
      <category>Tradition</category>
      
      <category>Food</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>Food</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
